<resources>
    <string name="app_name">DMesh</string>
    <string name="title_activity_main">DMesh</string>
    <string name="setup_enable"><b>Enable Mesh service.</b><br/>
        <p>A background service will discover nearby nodes, and register with
            the mesh control plane. This allows local applications on the
            device using DMesh API, SOCKS5 or HTTP PROXY to exchange messages
            and streams to communicate with other mesh nodes.</p>
        <p>If disabled, the DMesh service will exit and nothing will run until
        the service is enabled again. The random identity of the node will
        be reset.</p>
    </string>
    <string name="setup_vpn"><b>Capture all traffic using VPN.</b>
        Traffic from all applications on the device will be intercepted.
        Mesh addresses will be routed trough mesh. Normal egress traffic will use the
        internet connection of the device. If the device is lacks an internet
        connection the DMesh service will attempt to create tunnels using
        reachable nodes.
        <p>Enabling this option will require user to allow VPN permissions.
        It is not possible to use 2 VPNs at the same time - if you are using
        a different VPN, disable this option. Applications can still use DMesh
        by setting SOCKS or HTTP_PROXY.</p>
    </string>
    <string name="setup_wifi">
        <b>Use Wifi and Bluetooth to extend the mesh</b> <br/>
        Enabling the option will request Location permission - scanning and
        extending the mesh may reveal the Wifi/BLE MAC address. Some devices
        do not rotate the MAC address and that may allow tracking the device
        every time it is using Wifi. Scanning only happens if the device doesn\'t
        have an internet connection and attempts to create a mesh with other
        nearby devices. If this option is enabled, a device with internet
        connection may become a gateway for nearby devices, and may propagate
        messages to other nodes in the mesh.

    </string>
    <string name="setup_vpn_ext" >
        Use the external VPN server. WIP - testing only.
        Will require a user-configured egress server (exit node), for
        all non-mesh, non-local traffic. Currently the registration server
        is used.
    </string>
</resources>
